The past holds the key!
The Cutter is a action, adventure, thriller film directed by William Tannen.
A former cop turned Los Angeles P.I.
takes on a case of a missing diamond cutter that leads him on an adventure of love
and villainy spanning of mob to the present day Jewelry District.
John Shepherd, played by Chuck Norris.
Elizabeth Teller, played by Joanna Pacula.
Dirk, played by Daniel Bernhardt.
Issac Teller, played by Bernie Kopell.
Parks, played by Todd Jensen.
Sergeant, played by John T. Woods.
The Cutter is a 2005 American direct-to-video action film directed by Bill Tannen, and starring
Chuck Norris, Joanna Pacuła, Daniel Bernhardt, Bernie Kopell and Marshall R.
After a deadly kidnapping rescue gone wrong, a guilt ridden detective recruits his specialized SWAT
team to successfully rescue an aged diamond cutter from the hands of a murderous thief.
The film explores themes of shootout, diamond cutter, shoulder holster.
The tone is intense.